Come on, man. Help me do this.
快点,伙计.教教我玩这个.
No,no. Let's get this straight.
不,不.咱们先把话说清楚.
I am not going to help you learn to juggle.
我可不打算帮你学杂耍.
I'm not going to waste my time.
我不想浪费时间.
You don't listen.
你根本就不听.
-What?  -See? You never listen.
-什么?  -瞧,你从来就不听.
You're not really interested.
你并不是真的感兴趣.
Lately you're on some other planet, Danny.
最近你好像在另一个星球上,Danny.
Your body is here, but your mind is on Pluto.
你的身体在这儿,但你的脑子在冥王星上.
I'd rather teach someone who wants to learn.
我宁可教那些想学的人.
Nathan, it's not brain surgery.
Nathan,这不是大脑手术.
It's juggling.
只是杂耍而已.
And guess what? You still can't do it.
你猜这么着? 你仍然不会.
OK, OK, OK. I'm sorry.
好,好,好.对不起.
I'll listen better. I'll work harder.
我会更认真听你讲.我会更卖力些的.
Oh no. It's the 2 a.m. rush.
Oh 不.又是凌晨2点繁忙时刻.
Kinko's. This is Nathan. Can I help you?
Kinko复印社.我是Nathan.有什么能帮你的?
We're open all night.
我们通宵营业.
Yes, we do bulk copies.
是的,我们承接批量复印.
Sure. Let me get you the price list...
当然.让我给您拿价目表...
Ahh, tell them we're busy.
Ahh,告诉他们我们很忙.
We're swamped. Tell them to go away.
我们应付不过来.叫他们走开.
You know what? It's your lucky night.
您知道吗?今晚是您的幸运之夜.
Let me hand you over to my colleague.
让我把你交给我的同事.
He's our vice-president in charge of bulk copies
他是我们的副总裁,负责批量复印的工作.
and he can answer all of your questions.
他可以回答您所有的问题.
His name is Danny.
他叫Danny.
Hello. Yep. 7 cents.
您好.是的.7美分.
100. Sure. Yep. Bye.
100份.当然.好的.再见.